<ModMetaData>
  <name>What's Wrong - Colonist Needs Tracker</name>
  <author>ProgrammerLily</author>
  <description>
    What's Wrong - Colonist Needs Tracker is a powerful utility mod for RimWorld 1.6 that helps you keep your colony running smoothly by tracking all unmet needs across your colonists in real time.
    
    Features:
    • Adds a dedicated tab to the main UI, accessible at any time, showing a summary of all colonists with unmet needs (food, rest, recreation, medical, mood, and more).
    • Instantly see which colonists are missing critical resources, such as beds, tables, chairs, food, recreation sources, and more.
    • Click any need in the tracker window to jump directly to the affected colonist for fast intervention.
    • Provides actionable tutorial hints and designator shortcuts to help you resolve common issues (e.g., build a stove, place a table, create a growing zone).
    • Supports modded content: detects needs and objects from popular expansions and mods, including Royalty, Biotech, and Vanilla Expanded modules.
    • Smart detection for special zones (growing, fishing, stockpile, dumping) and modded buildings.
    • Fully compatible with RimWorld 1.6 and future updates.
    • Lightweight, performance-friendly, and designed for both new and veteran players.
    
    Usage:
    - Open the "What's Wrong" tab at the bottom of the screen to view all unmet needs.
    - Click on any listed need to jump to the colonist or open the relevant build/designator menu.
    - Use the provided hints to quickly address issues before they escalate.
    
    Compatibility:
    - Works with all major DLCs and most mods that add new needs or buildings.
    - No game balance changes; purely a UI and utility enhancement.
    
    For feedback, bug reports, or suggestions, please visit the mod's GitHub page or Steam Workshop listing.
    Github: https://github.com/sam2332/Rimworld-WhatsWrong
  </description>
  <packageId>whatswrong.programmerlily.com</packageId>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
    <li>VanillaExpanded.VFEFishing</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <modVersion>1.0.2</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>